{
    "subject": "resource/Drew_Sidora",
    "predicate": "ontology/activeYearsEndYear",
    "object": "1995",
    "human_readable": "Drew Sidora's active years ended in 1995.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9571659564971924,
            "question": "When did Drew Sidora's active years end?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9356051683425903,
            "question": "Was Drew Sidora active in the entertainment industry after 1995?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8276395797729492,
            "question": "What events might have influenced the end of Drew Sidora's active years?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7641116976737976,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Drew Sidora's work before 1995?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7441024780273438,
            "question": "Can we speculate on why Drew Sidora chose to stop working in 1995?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7343733310699463,
            "question": "Can we assume Drew Sidora retired from their profession in 1995?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7309960722923279,
            "question": "Are there any known projects or accomplishments from Drew Sidora released after 1995?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5976923704147339,
            "question": "Did Drew Sidora's career span several decades?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.521955132484436,
            "question": "What was the approximate timeframe of Drew Sidora's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3226667642593384,
            "question": "What type of work was Drew Sidora involved in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Drew Sidora's active years ended in 1995.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5592_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the approximate timeframe of Drew Sidora's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5592_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Drew Sidora's career span several decades?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5592_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any known projects or accomplishments from Drew Sidora released after 1995?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5592_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5592_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5592_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5592_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5592_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5592_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5592_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5592_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5592_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5592_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5592_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that it does not provide any direct or indirect evidence to support the claim that \"Drew Sidora's active years ended in 1995.\" In fact, one of the documents mentions that Drew starred as a main cast member on JD Lawrence's Community Service (2013), One Love (2014), and Hindsight (2015).\n\nTherefore, my response is:\n\n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information that supports the claim that Drew Sidora's active years as an actress ended in 1995. The provided context mentions her acting roles, including a small role in a TV movie at age nine and later roles in various TV series, but does not indicate when she stopped being actively involved in the entertainment industry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}